uh a quick video about music on live
stream the reason I don't do music on
the live stream anymore well I'm coding
is because people want to listen to
their own music number one number two
people are uh you know it is a copyright
thing and we are still questioning
whether YouTube even allows dropping the
music from TR you know b 2 like you can
do with twitch we don't even know if
it's possible but it might be but who
cares because you really don't want
music while I'm talking because I may be
too light might be too loud might be too
low you might not like the music the
music misses up transcription there's
just a million reasons not to do it it
makes it it makes it so that the videos
that I make and and you can't clip the
videos you can't put them out someplace
else um actually if there's music on it
disables clipping by default
automatically on Twitch there's a
million reasons to not stream with any
music in the background even copyright
free music a lot of people enjoy a nice
little Ambiance and stuff like that and
that's fantastic I do too but add it
yourself add your own music while you're
watching then and that way you don't
ever have to be afraid of there being uh
us talking at the same time right so
while we're talking you know thing like
that uh however there are times when I
put on really great music and when I do
that that's usually just a a coding
session and I deliberately don't talk
during those because I don't want
anybody I want somebody to be able to
put their own music on and not be afraid
of missing the audio from me so that I
can actually you know coat away and
listen to whatever music I want and not
really care and kind of be in DJ mode so
that's where I stand on the music thing
um I I even even copyright free music uh
in the you know light music in the
background I think is a bad thing I
don't think you should do that when you
live stream I hate it when people do
that uh this is a lesson I've learned
over four years that's really been hard
learned and and I'm just telling you why
so